American Society for Cell Biology records
American Society for Cell Biology records
- Series V. Committees, 1974-1994; 417 folders (12.75 linear feet)
  - Subseries V.B. Minorities Affairs Committee, 1984-1993; 197 folders (5.25 linear feet)
    - Travel Awards/Applications Withdrawn 1992 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Travel Awards/Correspondence 1992 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Travel Awards/Disbursement Totals 1992 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Travel Awards/Evaluations 1992 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Travel Awards/Registration and Housing 1992 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Travel Awards/Reimbursements to Students 1992 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Budget 1993 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Cold Spring Harbor Lab 1993 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence/Dr. Wyche 1993/1-1993/5 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence/Dr. Wyche 1993/6-1993/12 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence/General 1993 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Friday Harbor Laboratories 1993 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Letter to MARC Program Directors 1993 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - MBL/ASCB Student Program/Roles and Responsibilities 1993 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - MBL/Applications A-L 1993 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - MBL/Applications M-Z 1993 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - MBL/Applicants/Accepted (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - MBL/Applicants/List 1993 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - MBL/Applicants Rejected 1993 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - MBL/Correspondence 1993 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - MBL/Correspondence/Course Directors 1993 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - MBL/Catalog 1993 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - MBL/Evaluations 1993 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - MBL/Luncheon/Attendees 1993 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - MBL/Luncheon/Invited Guests 1993 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - MBL/Luncheon/Planning 1993 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - MBL/Luncheon/Responses 1993 (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - MBL/Requests For Applications 1993 (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - MBL/Student Funding 1993 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - MBL/Summer Course Info 1993 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Annual Meeting 1993/12/13 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Interim Meeting 1993/4/7 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - NSF Grant Proposal From Dr. Wyche 1993 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - New Membership 1993 (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Proposal For Lecture Series and Technical Workshops 1993 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Symposium/Morehouse School of Medicine 1993 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - Summer Program/Correspondence 1993 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Summer Program/Response Forms 1993 (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - Travel Awards/Applications A-L 1993 (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - Travel Awards/Applications M-Z 1993 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Travel Awards/Applicants Address List 1993 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Travel Awards/Awardees 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Student Awards/Correspondence 1993 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Travel Awards/Evaluations and Rankings 1993 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Travel Awards/Jo Anne Del Rio 1993 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Travel Awards/Acceptance/Award Letters 1993 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Travel Awards/Rejection Letters 1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Travel Awards/Waitlist Letters 1993 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Travel Awards/Rosa I Rodriguez 1993 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Travel Awards/Student Reimbursement 1993 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Visiting Scientists For MARC Institutions 1993 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Report To Council/Dr. Wyche 1993 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Subseries V.C. Women in Cell Biology, 1974-1994; 27 folders (.75 linear feet)
    Correspondence, memos, minutes, reports, applications, resumes, questionnaire, and newsletters organized by subject and then in date order.
    - Committee Elections 1993 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1975-1979 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1980-1989 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1993 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Handbook 1989/How To Get A Job (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Minutes and Reports 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Minutes and Reports 1990 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Minutes and Reports 1993 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Minutes and Reports 1994 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Newsletter 1974-1979 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Newsletter 1980-1981 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Questionnaire 1976-1978 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Summer Conference 1989/Applications (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - WICB Award/Awardees (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - WICB Award 1993/Evaluations and Rankings (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - WICB Award/1993-Letter to Nominat (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - WICB Awards/Logo (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - WICB Award 1993/Nominees A-H (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - WICB Award 1993/Nominees K-L (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - WICB Award 1993/Nominees M-R (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - WICB Award 1993/Nominees S-W (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - WICB Award/Junior Award Nominees 1993 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - WICB Award/Senior Award Nominees 1993 (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Workshop 1990/Careers in Biological Sciences/Applications A-C (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Workshop 1990/Careers in Biological Sciences/Applications D-G (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Workshop 1990/Careers in Biological Sciences/Advancement For Women and Minorities/Applications H-J (Box 75, Folder 39)